# Alex Purser

1 St James Terrace, TR10 8NW 07597 901217 | ajpurser32@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

I am a hard-working and naturally determined person with a passion for the technology industry. I have worked in many team environments and have shown my skills and cooperation with each, overcoming challenges through good communication and drive for completion. I can work well in scheduled deadlines and under pressure.

#### **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

## **BSc Year 2 | Falmouth University**

2022 - Present

- BSc Computer Science Year 2

This is the course I am currently enrolled in.

### A Levels | Longsands Sixth Form

2020 - 2022

- BTEC Computer Science (D\*D\*)
- Mathematics (C)
- Physics (C)

UCAS Tariff - 176 points

## **GCSE | Longsands Academy**

2015 - 2020

- Mathematics (8) Computer Science (6)
- Biology (8) Economics (6)
- Physics (7)
  Further Mathematics (6)
  Chemistry (7)
  English Language (5)
  English Literature (5)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Games Tester | Universally Speaking**

Jun 2022 to Aug 2022

Universally Speaking is a capacity partner. Universally Speaking test video games for developers, returning useful feedback, and working with them until each video game is complete.

- Working as a team effectively to manage and complete client requests.
- Using software such as Jira to organise client requests and work through them efficiently.
- Working through multiple projects simultaneously and abiding by strict deadlines.
- Helping colleagues with client feedback and work management.

#### IT Service Work Placement | MASS Consultants Ltd.

Jan 2022 to Jul 2022

MASS is an independent technology company, trusted by highly secure organisations to provide advanced digital services and training that manages data and keeps information safe.

- Working as a team to manage and complete client requests.
- Working with others to organise stock levels and workspaces.
- Setting up computer systems for clients using BIOS and physical component installation.
- Managing client computer systems and devices.

# Sep 2021 to Dec 2021

#### **Customer Services Assistant | Central England Co-operative**

- Working as a team to ensure customer help and satisfaction.
- Effective customer communication.
- Helping manage stock levels.
- Taking in and recording deliveries.
- Working on the tills.
- Working with others to manage stock shelf life.

# **Festive Colleague | Tesco**

Nov 2020 to Dec 2020

- Working with others to ensure customer help and satisfaction.
- Managing stock levels.
- Effective customer communication and support.

#### **SKILLS**

My skills include:

- Strong understanding of Python, C#, HTML, and CSS.
- Strong customer communication skills.
- Usage of software such as Jira, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, and Unity.
- Ability to set up computer systems and other systems effectively.
- Strong team working skills.

### **ABOUT ME**

Volunteered at OpenDoorChurch St Neots. Each Sunday being tasked with PA management, such as setting up projectors, computer systems, and PA systems. Also learning cable management, presentation organisation, effective testing, and showcasing the presentation to the church.

Completed a work experience day with ARM. ARM is a software company located in Britain. During this, they taught me low level binary interpretation and the implementation of software into everyday systems.

Work experience with Xtreme360. Xtreme360 is a trampoline park company which employed me for a week. During this week, I worked as a team to clean and organise the park and ensure customer satisfaction.

#### **INTERESTS**

I have always been fascinated by the technology industry. Coding, game development and physical computer systems have always intrigued me. I first leaned Python and C# in Longsands Academy. I would end up going home to program my own algorithms and applications, experimenting each day with newly found functions and applications. Web development was a recent interest, having built two websites for my education. I want to understand as much as I can about technology and help implement it into as many people's lives as possible.

I have also always been sports heavy, often doing clubs and societies. Currently I focus on badminton and golf, which I aim to play either at least once a week. These sports are a great way for me to relax and relieve stress.

#### **REFERENCES**

Claire Chilton | Head of Computer science | claire.chilton@astrea-longsands.org | Longsands Academy

Melanie Paine | Mathematics teacher | melanie.paine@astrea-longsands.org | Longsands Academy